

JOHN JOHNSON

Software Developer



PROFILE

John Johnson Okah is an enthusiastic Software Developer with 3+ years of experience and a focus on web design, artificial intelligence, and machine learning.



Abuja, Nigeria



+234-706-696-3636



jjokah@pm.me



Disposify

A web app that connects waste collectors to customers for seamless waste disposal.

The Good Shopper

A fully featured online shop with product checkout, order placement and e-payment.

Graceland Management System

A web based hotel management system that takes inventory of incoming and outgoing stocks/sales.



@jjokah



@jjokah_



in @jjokah



jjokah.github.io



EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Wiitech Services | Aug 2018 - Jan 2019

 Built a Hotel Management System with python and managed some sites with cpanel

Web Developer

BuildforSDG | Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

· As the lead developer on the facebook-andela hackathon, I used django to build a Waste Disposal System

Software Developer

MAGNISALE | since Dec 2020

• Manage an Ecommerce site and designed websites with python



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

University of Nigeria Nsukka | 2014 - 2018

• BSc. Certificate in Computer Science



SKILLS

Backend Dev. Frontend Dev. Design Algorithm Machine Learning Cloud Computing